Guide to the REPOhistory Archive MSS.113
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Projects
  - Subseries F: Out From Under the King George Hotel
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Budgeting/planning, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Jim Costanzo's notes and correspondence A., undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Jim Costanzo's notes and correspondence B., undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Research - Deeds and city/county documents, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Research - articles, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Research - photocopies of photo documentation of renovations, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Research - handwritten notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Research - Neill Bogan, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Research - NY Public Library call slips, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Research - bibliography, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Proofs of artwork, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Subseries G: Civil Disturbances
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - legal matters, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 'Lisa Knauer folder', undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Research, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Mayor Giuliani and artist Lederman, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Research - legal briefs, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - New York Lawyers for Public Interest (NYLPI), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Proofs for artwork, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Printer's proofs, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Misc., undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Meeting minutes, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Community board meetings, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Budgeting/planning, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Project outlines, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Proposals, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Research, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Subseries H: Circulations
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Legal documents, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - REPO resume, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - List of proposals and contributors, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Budgeting/planning, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Project outlines, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Timelines, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Bio of members and artists, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Research - "People Notes", undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Research A., undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Research B., undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Research C., undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - 'Map Site Info', undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Drafts of drawings and texts, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Original art, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Web information, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Maps, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - 'Education/outreach ideas', undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Slide list, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Related announcements, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Catalogues, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Misc., undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Subseries I: Related Projects
    - African American Burying Ground procession, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Anti-racism conference, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Artists and writers out loud, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Banff center library exhibition catalogue, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 'Building Histories' at Apex Art, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - East Harlem project, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - History Happened Here conference, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Hudson River Middle School residency, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hudson River Middle School - original art, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hudson River Middle School - ephemera [see also Series IX: Ephemera], undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Labor History Happened Here, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Whitney Museum downtown "City of Power" exhibition, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Museum of the City of New York - meetings and proposals, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - New Museum education project, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Parasite at the Drawing Center, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - DIA proposals for NYC Customs House, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - REPOHistory website proposals, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ruins in Reverse - CEPA gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sprawl exhibition - Atlanta, GA, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Urban Encounters - correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Urban Renewal - correspondence (legal), undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Urban Renewal - grant proposals, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Urban Renewal - project outlines, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Urban Renewal - planning, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Urban Renewal - budgeting, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Urban Encounters - budget book, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Urban Encounters - Research, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Urban Encounters - PAD/D, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Urban Encounters - New Museum, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Urban Renewal - Proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Urban Encounters - Misc., undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Veiled Histories conference, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Whittier sign project, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Conferences and panel discussions about REPO, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Exhibitions which include REPO, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Exhibitions of members and friends of REPO, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Series III: Publicity and Promotion
  - Promotional packet - general, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Press about the collective, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Articles - Lower Manhattan Sign Project (LMSP), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Press release - LMSP, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Walking tours - LMSP, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Promotional - Lower Manhattan Sign Project (Box 10, Folder 5a)
  - Unpublished articles/reviews - LMSP, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Press release - Choice Histories, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Articles/reviews - Choice Histories, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Press release - Queer Spaces, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Reviews - Queer Spaces, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Press release - Entering Buttermilk Bottom, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Articles/reviews - Entering Buttermilk Bottom, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Public review/comments - Entering Buttermilk Bottom, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Reviews - Voices of Renewal, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Promotion - Out From Under King George, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Press release - Civil Disturbances, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Articles - Civil Disturbances, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Press release - Urban Encounters, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Reviews - Urban Encounters, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Press release - Circulations, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Articles/reviews - Circulations, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Series IV: Theoretical material
  - Greg Sholette's files - "Theory": narratives, talks, articles, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Labor history images, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 1989-92 research, 1989-1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Art work, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Alternative/radical histories, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Readings in race and class, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Readings for East Harlem project, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Readings for Museum City of New York project, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Readings in office file, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Linking American for the Arts, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Series V: Members Files
  - Subseries A: Members Files - Ed Eisenberg
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Meeting minutes A, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Meeting minutes B, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Project outlines, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Budgeting/planning information, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Atlanta installation receipts, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Groundworks receipts, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Mac computer, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Funding/grant proposal, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Art show announcements, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Art show announcements, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Art show announcements, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Art show announcements, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Art show announcements, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Art show announcements, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Art show announcements, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Art show announcements, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Art show announcements, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Art show announcements, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Art show announcements, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Art show announcements, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Art show announcements, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Art show announcements, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Art show announcements, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Art show announcements, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Art show announcements (n. d.), undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Review of art shows, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Artists and Writers Out Loud (AWOL), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Coalition for nuclear-free harbor A., undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Coalition for nuclear-free harbor B., undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Coalition for nuclear-free harbor C., undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Coalition for nuclear-free harbor D., undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Coalition for nuclear-free harbor E., undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Coalition for nuclear-free harbor F., undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Source material - AIDS, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Source material - nuclear weapon accidents, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 'Ed's source material' A., undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 'Ed's source material' B., undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 'Ed's source material' C., undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 'Ed's source material' D., undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - 'Ed's source material' E., undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Readings A., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Readings B., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Readings C., undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Readings D., undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Readings E., undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Readings F., undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Readings G., undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Memorial projects, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Village voice ad, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Groundworks, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Groundworks, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Ephemera, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - PADD (Policital Art Documentation/Distribution)- Correspondence, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - PAD/D - Research, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - PAD/D - photos and artwork, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - PAD/D - bank statements, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Stencil [OVERSIZE], undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Members files - Greg Sholette
    - History Project - original proposal, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Planning documents and narratives, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Waking Up drafts, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Articles and artwork by Greg Sholette, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Announcement of Greg's works, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Articles/reviews of Greg and Janet's work, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Literature on foundations and programs, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Syllabi on courses taught by Greg, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Resume, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Subseries C: Members files - Tom Klem
    - Correspondence A., undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence B., undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Drafts of text, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Announcements/promo, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Catalogues, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - 'Tom's outreach folder', undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Budgeting/planning, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Whittier Community Dialogue Sign Project, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Art commission of the city of New York, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Insurance certificates, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Source material and research, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Slide list, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Maps, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Office supply catalogue, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Research, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Project outlines, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Community board meetings, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Department of Transportation - New York City, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Meeting minutes, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Site proposals, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Notebook/planner, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Photos, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Sholette's art folder, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Mailing list, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - REPO contracts folder, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - REPO/NYLPI folder, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Temporary files folder, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Reviews of Tom's work, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Misc., undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Subseries D: Members files - Jim Costanzo
    - Correspondence - email and written, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Grant applications and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Abstracts and drafts of articles, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Photos of meeting - 12/17/90, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Photos of meeting - 7/29/91, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Michael Richards - REPO member who died 9/11/01 in WTC, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Documents from the website by Jim Costanzo, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Series VI: Slides and Photos
  - Lower Manhattan Sign Project, undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Choice Histories, undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Out From Under the King George Hotel, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Circulations, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Entering Buttermilk Bottom - Research - Photos of Atlanta, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Entering Buttermilk Bottom - by Jim Costanzo, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Entering Buttermilk Bottom - Cardboard mounted photos, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Voices of Renewal, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Civil Disturbances, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Circulations, undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Ed Eisenberg, undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - PAD/D, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Not for Sale - show by Tom Klem, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Black photo box; Photos and negatives of parades and openings of REPO projects; Slides of photos used in grant applications., undated (Box 15, Folder data_value_missing_7e534a683d224fae6e1561a73fde0b82)
  - Black photo box; Slides of photos of REPO members working and installing., undated (Box 16, Folder data_value_missing_7932fd7c08ac938a1b89b3430b4f9887)
  - Black photo box; Ed Eisenberg - Groundworks., undated (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_9949e593ce71c36627b1c219ec538608)
- Series VII: Video, Audio, and Electronic.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  - Lower Manhattan Sign Project (VHS videocassette and audio tape), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    General
    DVD Access Copy available.
  - Choice Histories - "In Defense of Roe" by ACLU (VHS videocassette) -, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Entering Buttermilk Bottom (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Atlanta - "Atlanta Tape 1 and 2" (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta interviews - Mrs. Brayboy, Mrs. Humphery, and Mrs. Sutton (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta interviews - Thad Olive, Ron Grier, Mrs. Sheats, and A. B. Cooper (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Atlanta interviews - Malone (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Tom Klem - "Tracey Takes on... Age", "Game Plans", and "Ooh La La" (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - PAD/D - "PAD/D Presents.. ." (VHS videocassette), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Magnetic disks - REPO general, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Magnetic disks - Atlanta (Lisa Knauer), undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Magnetic disks - Atlanta, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Magnetic disks - Bogan/Neville signs, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Magnetic disks - LMSP Sign templates, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Magnetic disks - Entering Buttermilk Bottom, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Magnetic disks - Bogan/Ledwith, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Magnetic disks - Lisa Knauer, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Magnetic disks - (zipdisks) from Greg Sholette, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Series VIII: Artwork
  Scope and Contents note
  For the purposes of description, each sign is identified by the first sentence of text on the front of each sign.
  - Subseries A: Queer Spaces
    All signs are pink triangles featuring the words Queer Spaces across the top and the words Places of Struggle Places of Strength running left to right on the other two edges of the triangle. On each sign the text ends with the REPOhistory logo and the sign number at the apex of the triangle.
    - Sign 1: The first gay rights demonstration in New York City occurred on September 19, 1964 in front of the Whitehall Street Induction Center., undated (Box 23, Box 22)
    - Sign 2: On March 24, 1987, The AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACT UP) held its first demonstration at this corner., undated (Box 23)
    - Sign 3: New York City's Gay and Lesbian Civil Rights Bill was introduced in the City Council on January 6, 1971., undated (Box 23)
    - Sign 4: The Gay Activists Alliance occupied the former Firehouse at 99 Wooster Street from May 1971 until October 1974, when it was destroyed by arson., undated (Box 23)
    - Sign 5: The Daughters of Bilitis, one of the earliest lesbian political organizations, had offices at 30 Charlton Street for several years, beginning in 1963., undated (Box 23, Box 22)
    - Sign 6: Bonnie and Clyde's, a lesbian bar, stood at 82 West 3rd Street from the early seventies through the mid-eighties., undated (Box 23, Box 22)
    - Sign 7: Marsha P. Johnson 1945-1992 born Malcolm Michaels Stonewall Veteran, performer, panhandler, prostitute, Warhol Model, on July 6, 1992, the body of this legendary drag queen was found floating in the river near this site., undated (Box 23, Box 22)
    - Sign 8: In 1966, the State Liquor Authority imposed a 30-day suspension on Julius', the landmark bar located at 159 West Tenth St., after an undercover policeman had reported that the bar permitted gay men to "consort themselves in an offensive and indecent manner contrary to good morals.", undated (Box 23, Box 22)
    - Sign 9: In 1888, financier James Everard converted an old church at 28 W. 28th Street into a Turkish bathhouse., undated (Box 23, Box 22)
  - Subseries B: Lower Manhattan Sign Project
    All signs are printed on the front and back. In cases in which text appears on both sides it is noted in the transcription, otherwise the text appears only on the back. All signs end with one or two boxed questions in the lower left corner on the back with the sign number and the REPOhistory logo in the lower right corner. Note: For this project, the archive does not have a copy of sign number 35.
    - Introduction: The Lower Manhattan Sign Project, 1992; cuid6230; 1 item one sign (Folder VIII, 1, Object MSS.113.cuid6230, Folder 74)
      Information signs.
    - Sign 1: What is all-inclusive history? (2 copies), 1992; cuid6231; 2 items two signs (Folder VIII, 2, Object MSS.113.cuid6231a-b)
    - Sign 2: Spirits of America (2 copies), 1992; cuid6232; 2 items two signs (Folder VIII, 3, Object MSS.113.cuid6232a-b)
    - Sign 3A: "They Died Very Stubbornly" wrote justice Daniel Horsmanden of those executed during the New York Conspiracy or "Great Negro Plot" of 1741, 1992; cuid6233; 1 item one sign (Folder VIII, 4, Object MSS.113.cuid6233)
    - Sign 3B: The New York Conspiracy of 1741, 1992; cuid6267; 1 item one sign (Item MSS.113.cuid6267)
    - Sign 3C: Rumors of revolt…fueled the inquest into the "Great Negro Plot" of 1741, 1992; cuid6266; 1 item one sign (Item MSS.113,cuid6266)
    - Sign 4: Leisler's Rebellion (3 copies), 1992; cuid6234; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 5, Object MSS.113.cuid6234a-c)
    - Sign 5: These are the remains of the gilded King George III equestrian statue after patriots pulled it from its pedestal here on July 9, 1775. (2 copies), 1992; cuid6235; 2 items two signs (Folder VIII, 6, Object MSS.113.cuid6235a-b)
    - Sign 6: On the fourth day of the month of March in the year nineteen ninety-one, three homeless Americans passed a very cold and bitter night on this spot in lower manhattan. (3 copies), 1992; cuid6236; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 7, Object MSS.113.cuid6236a-c)
    - Sign 7: Then, accidentally, due to a mistake in the filing system, the married father of three children was drafted, he lived a long time, maybe three months and killed several guerrillas, two by strangulation, two by being a crack shot, and one in self-defense. (3 copies), 1992; cuid6237; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 8, Object MSS.113.cuid6237a-c)
    - Sign 8: The shoreline of Nieuw Amsterdam began at Pearl Street. (2 copies), 1992; cuid6238; 2 items two signs (Folder VIII, 9, Object MSS.113.cuid6238a-b)
    - Sign 9: Summer 1990-Nelson Mandela visits New York (3 copies), 1992; cuid6239; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 10, Object MSS.113.cuid6239a-c)
    - Sign 10: "Esta gente viven endios" C.C. 1492 (3 copies), 1992; cuid6240; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 11, Object MSS.113.cuid6240a-c)
    - Sign 11: Manhattan before the Dutch exchanged it to the English in 1667 for Surinam, South America, after having only leased it from the Delaware Indians. (3 copies), 1992; cuid6241; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 12, Object MSS.113.cuid6241a-c)
    - Sign 12: Where is the fabulous wealth of India, the spices, silks and gems which Columbus sought? (3 copies), 1992; cuid6242; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 13, Object MSS.113.cuid6242a-c)
    - Sign 13: Exchange Place (2 copies), 1992; cuid6243; 2 items two signs (Folder VIII, 14, Object MSS.113.cuid6243a-b)
    - Sign 14: Advantages of an Unregulated Free Market Economy (3 copies), 1992; cuid6244; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 15, Object MSS.113.cuid6244a-c)
    - Sign 15: False Democracy (3 copies), 1992; cuid6245; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 16, Object MSS.113.cuid6245a-c)
    - Sign 16: How do things get explained away so easily (2 copies), 1992; cuid6246; 2 items two signs (Folder VIII, 17, Object MSS.113.cuid6246a-b)
    - Sign 17: Who owns your life? (3 copies), 1992; cuid6247; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 18, Object MSS.113.cuid6247a-c)
    - Sign 18: The Meal and Slave Market, 1992; cuid6248; 1 item one sign (Folder VIII, 19, Object MSS.113.cuid6248)
    - Sign 19: Women's Trade Union League (3 copies), 1992; cuid6249; 3 items three signs (Folder VIII, 20, Object MSS.113.cuid6249a-c)
    - Sign 20: The Earliest Chinese Community in New York, 1992; cuid6250; 1 item one sign (Folder VIII, 21, Object MSS.113.cuid6250)